<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">


  <blockquote class="stu-note">
    <p>The specification herewith documented is for the time being a working specification, and may
  not be used for any implementation purposes. No liability can be inferred from the use or misuse
  of this specification, or its consequences.</p>
  </blockquote>

  <a name="scope"></a>
  <h3>Scope</h3>
  <p>
  This is the Hospital Dischareg Report HL7 FHIR Implementation Guide for the XpanDH project,
  created to assist the work of the pilots for the <a href="#adoption-domains">XpanDH exprimentation
  bubbles</a>. </p>


  <blockquote class="dragon">
    <p>This specification has been created to contribute to the development of the European EHRxF
  for this domain.</p>
    <p>
      <b>This guide is not intended to replace or override possible future standard guides or any
  other Implementation Guide that will be specified by MyHealth@Eu and/or JA-09; but to provide
  support for its development.</b>
    </p>
  </blockquote>


  <a name="project"></a>
  <h3>The project</h3>
  <a
    name="mission"></a>
  <h4>The mission</h4>
  <p>Help individuals and organizations successfully adopt
  the European Electronic Health Record Exchange Format (EEHRxF) in a way that is empowering and
  supportive.</p>

  <a name="how"></a>
  <h4>How to:</h4>
  <p>Mobilizing and building capacity to ensure the
  widespread adoption of the European Electronic Health Records Exchange Format (EEHRxF) across
  Europe. </p>
  <p>More details in <a href="https://xpandh-project.iscte-iul.pt/">XpanDH Web Site</a>

  </p>

  <a
    name="adoption-domains"></a>
  <h3>XpanDH Adoption Domains/X-Bubbles</h3>
  <a name="mission"></a>

  <a
    name="what-is-adoption-domain"></a>
  <h4>What is:</h4>
  <p>An EEHRxF adoption domain could be
  considered as an instantiation of a use case, with a specific case application, that has meaning
  from a health system or clinical perspective, with defined implementable requirements (simple if
  only one EEHRxF priority category is uses or composite if data from more than one is required),
  that satisfies all the conditions for users to be ready to implement data exchange in conformity
  to EEHRxF guidelines and specifications </p>
  <p>XpanDH will exercise a set of adoption domains,
  involving Hospitals, Regional/National organziation, vendors,.., thorugh experimentaion bubbles
  (in the Hpandh jargon called X-Bubbles)</p>

  <a name="covered-adoption-domain"></a>
  <h4>Adoption
  domains / X-Bubbles covered by this guide:</h4>
  <ul>
    <li>X-Bubble 3: NCZI; organisation to organisation (national). Exchange of discharge reports
  between different organisations, such as a hospital and a GP or between a hospital local to the
  patient and a specialist centre treating a disease such as a cancer, in order to enable each
  clinical actor to be well informed and contribute accurately to the same patient care pathway.</li>
    <li>X-Bubble 4: CHUP; organisation to patient (national. Communicate discharge reports from a
  hospital to the patient (within the same country) so that they can be informed, raise questions if
  needed, share this information with other caregivers and take any self-care actions indicated in
  the report.</li>
    <li>X-Bubble 5: KETEKNY; organisation to national authority.Communicate discharge reports from a
  hospital to a national authority to support reimbursement decisions or to contribute content to a
  national registry.</li>
    <li>X-Bubble 6: KETEKNY; national authority to organisation. The national authority communicates
  discharge reports to a hospital treating a patient, that it has previously received from other
  hospitals treating that patient, to enable a smooth transfer and continuity of care (e.g. if a
  patient moves home).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>More details on X-Bubbles and Adoption Doamin in XpanDH
  deliverable D1.4 and D4.1 <a href="https://xpandh-project.iscte-iul.pt/">XpanDH Web Site</a>
  </p>

  <a name="x-versions"></a>
  <h3>Cross Version Analysis</h3>

{% include cross-version-analysis.xhtml %}

  <a name="global"></a>
  <h3>Global Profiles</h3>

{% include globals-table.xhtml %}


  <a name="ip-statements"></a>
  <h3>IP Statements</h3>

{% include ip-statements.xhtml %}

</div>